cvplaza.com 2012-12-06

# Privacy Statement - CV Plaza

CVPLAZA.COM knows that you care about information about you is stored, used or shared and we appreciate your trust in us to do that carefully and sensibly.

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

###  **(1) What information do we collect?**

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information:

(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views, website navigation and search terms);

(b) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters; and

(c) any other information that you choose to send to us;

###  **(2) Cookies**

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser.

The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We may use both “session” cookies on the website.  We will use the session cookies to keep track of you whilst you navigate the website. Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser.

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website.  Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers.  The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information.  Google’s privacy policy is available at: <http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html>.

You can [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) to find out how you can control cookies. However, blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.

###  **(3) Using your personal information**

Personal information submitted to us via this website, which is extremely limited, will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

(a) administer the website;

(b) enable your use of the services available on the website;

(c) send you general (non-marketing) communications;

(d) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;

(e) provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;

(f) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website.

We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.

###  **(4) Policy amendments**

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website.  You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

###  **(5) Third party websites**

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.
